Guide to the Division of Continuing Education records, 1937-2003 RG0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Division of Continuing Education records
1937-2003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0016
21.25 Linear Feet
Collection includes video tapes of First Ladies Carter, Reagan, Bush, Clinton for "President's spouse," seminars and program guides, continuing education for women, pamphlets, syllabi, reports, manuals, biographical files, photographs and continuing education for telecommunications.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials transfered to University Archives by Division of Continuing Education.
In 2017 Accession 2017.073 was added. This is from the Department of Telecommunications.
Historical Note
The Division of Continuing Education was the branch of the university dedicated to extended educational course and programs to the general population. These were not degree programs. Over the years there have been several nationally known programs such as Women's Studies.
This program grew from a highly successful Continuing Education for Women (CEW) project founded in 1965 and led by Professor Ruth Osborn. These CEW students, many of them college graduates influenced by the Women's Movement, wanted graduate work that would enable them to help other women. With demonstrated student demand, Dr. Osborn persuaded the administration to approve an interdisciplinary M.A. degree comparable to other Special Studies M.A. degrees in the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences.
Today this program is known as the College of Professional Studies.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include materials relating to the continuing education for Women program and Women's educational equity Act project, video tapes of First Ladies Carter, Reagan, Bush, Clinton for "President's spouse," seminars and program guides. Also included is adult education, continuing education for women, pamphlets, syllabi, reports, Abbie Smith correspondence, manuals, biographical files and photographs of Distinguished Alumni Award Winners and those nominated, faculty files, and course descriptions. The collection also contains documents related to the Telecommunications program that was offered through the Division of Continuing Education. The collection covers the years 1937 to 2003.
Collection Organization
Organized into four series: Continuing education for women, Videotapes, Continuing education files, Distinguished alumni awards.
Women; Presidents' spouses; Education; Photographs; Washington (D.C.); Telecommunication; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae; George Washington University; Osborn, Ruth Helm; George Washington University. Division of Continuing Education
- Continuing education for women, 1976-1977; RG0016 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of materials related to the continuing education for women program and women's educational equity act project. The materials range in date from 1976-1977.
  Formerly Acc#982.
- Videotapes, 1994; RG0016 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of video tapes of First Ladies Carter, Reagan, Bush, and Clinton for President's spouse seminars, and program guide. The materials date from 1994.
- Continuing education files, 1964-2003; RG0016 Series 3; 19.25 Linear Feet; 19.25 Linear feet
  This series consists of adult education, continuing education for women, and continuing education files including telecommunications. Materials include pamphlets, syllabi, reports, correspondence, and manuals. The materials range in date from 1964-2003.
  Arrangement
  Arranged by subject, then type, then chronologically.
  - Academic Programs-International Affairs at the war colleges, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Programs-Reviews, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration-Administrative memoranda, 1978 -1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration-Americ. management association information, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration-Columbian College off-campus credit courses, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administration-Development office, 1989 -1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administration-Policies and procedures, 1969 -1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administration-Program management, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administration-Registration, 1992 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adult Education-Advisory Committee on Adult Learning Services, 01/1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    General note
    Binder
  - Adult Education-Alternative education, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adult Education-Annual report, press release, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adult Education-Bulletins, articles, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adult Education-College Board, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adult Education-Commission for the Year 2000, 1885 ca. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adult Education-Four year program plan in D.C., 1990 -1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adult Education-Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adult Education-National conference on the adult learner, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adult Education-Pamphlets, articles, correspondence, 1976-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adult Education-Study, 1949 -1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agendas-notes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alumnae-Alumni support, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annotation-Annotated bibliography, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Fund, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Center for Career Education Workshops (CCEW) -Career opportunities, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CCEW -Organizational charts, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CCEW-Pamphlets, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CCEW-Staff meetings, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education for Women (CEW) - Budget, 1960-1970 ca. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CEW -Memos, policies, 1977 -1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - College of General Studies (CGS) - Counseling memos, 1971 -1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CGS- Personal memos, 1975 -1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CGS- Transition to CESS, 1975 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - CHRON-Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CHRON-Correspondence, 01/1992 --10/1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - College Board-Advisory Committee, 1987 -1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - College Board-OALS, 1989 -1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education-Annual Report, 1986 -1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Continuing Education-DCE, CCEW, off campus, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Continuing Education-Examination of Continuing Education at GWU, 11/1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education-Expository writing for treasury, 1969 -1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Continuing Education-External Degree, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Continuing Education-Guidelines, 1985 -1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Continuing Education-General accounting office, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Continuing Education-"George Calling", 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Continuing Education-History, bulletin, curriculum, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Continuing Education-Five year plan, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Continuing Education-Journal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Continuing Education-Marketing, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Continuing Education-National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA), 1989 -1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Continuing Education-NUCEA, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Continuing Education-Pamphlets, 1992 ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Continuing Education-Pamphlets, 1992 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Education-Pamphlets, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Continuing Education-Papers, press releases, annual report, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education-Plans to develop C.E. programs, 1989 -1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education-Program awards, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Continuing Education-Publications, 1990 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education-Publications, 1990 -1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Education-Summer school and graduate school programs, 1992 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Course Syllabus-Listing of curriculum and syllabuses, 1990 ca. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Course Syllabus-Listing of curriculum and syllabuses, 1990 ca. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Course Syllabus-Statistics 129P, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Course Syllabus-Varying curriculum, 08/1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dean-Council of Deans, agendas and notes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dean-Council of Deans, schedule, 1991 -1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dean-Council of Deans, schedule, 1992 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dean-Council of Deans, schedule, 1992 -1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dean-Dean Long, 1983 -1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dean-Dean Long, CCEW, 1981 -1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dean-Dean Long, five-year plan, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dean-Dean Long, meeting, 1981 -1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Dean-Dean Long, memorandums, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dean-Dean Long, memos, 1981 -1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dean-Dean Long, resignation (confidential), 1985 -1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dean-Dean's report, 1979 -1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Directory-Faculty, student, staff, 1990 ca. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Distance Education-Distance learning, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Distance Education-Teleconferencing, PBS adult learning satellite service, 1990 -1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Distance Education-Video training/instruction, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Education-Doctoral programs information, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Education-Educational planning questionnaires, 1960 ca. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Education-Filmmakers Library, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Education-Master of Arts programs, 1970 ca. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Education-Masters student handbook, 1995 -1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Education-Metropolitan Life survey of the Americ. teacher, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Education-Strategic planning, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Education-Teacher accreditation, 1970 ca. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Education-Teachers' instructional guides, workbooks, manuals, 1972 -1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Education-Undergraduate information, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Educational Speaking-Conferences, seminars, 1990 -1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Educational Speaking-N.H. Speaker notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Educational Speaking-Speeches, Presentations, 1989 -1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Educational Speaking-Symposiums & Colloquiums, 1982 -1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Senate, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Films for the Humanities and Sciences-Video Catalogue, 1990 -1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Finance-Budget Information, 1970 ca. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Finance-Budget & Performance Rating Forms, 1986 -1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Finance-Budget, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Finance-Briefs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Finance-Financial Reports GSCE, 1982 -1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Finance-Fringe benefits and Individual costs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Finance-Grant information, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Finance-GW financial affairs, 01/05/1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Finance-Income and expenditures, 1964 -1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Finance-Income history report, 1965 -1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Finance-UCLA NEH Grant, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fitness-Health issues, 1981 ca. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fitness-Executive fitness health center, 10/1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1992 -1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - GSAS-MS Management Information Systems Proposal, 1989 -1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Education & Human Development (GSEHD)-Faculty Retreat, 10/21/1999 --10/22/1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - GSEHD-Final Examination for the Degree of Doctor of Education, 08/13/1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - GSEHD-Proposal for the Doctor of Philosophy degree, 10/06/1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - GWU-Community Commitment booklet, 1998 ca. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - GWU-General information, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - GWU-Research, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - GWU-Study abroad, 1992 -1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - GWU-TQM, 1992 -1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - IDLCON-Keynote speech by President Trachtenberg, 04/19/1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - ISN-Access procedures, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - JAIM, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jossey-Bass chapter, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Jossey-Bass publication notices, 1991 -1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Labor Statistics-Demographics, 1988 -1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Labor Statistics-Employment information, includes minutes, 1973 -1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Legal Assistance Program (LAP)-correspondence, 1977 -1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - LAP-Correspondence, 1977 -1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - LAP-Graduation, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Landscape Architect Assistant Program-Income, 1976 -1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - LERN-Annual reports, program guide, 1990 -1992 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - LERN-Newsletters, 1992 -1993 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Luncheon, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Mailing List-Catalogue, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Medic. Records Analysis, 1976 -1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Mail Logs, 02/06/1991 --05/15/1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mail Logs, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mail Logs, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mail Logs, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Noncredit-Completed noncredit, 1976 -1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NUCEA-Issue Alert, 1989 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Organizations-Bureau of National Affairs, 1991 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Organizations-Center for Centers, 1992 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Organizations-D.C. National College Fair, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Organizations-G.W. Crystal City Center, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Organizations-HumRRO International, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Organizations-Kuwaiti Delegation, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Organizations-NASA, 1977 -1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Organizations-National Recreation & Park Association, 1976 -1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Organizations-National Research Council, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Organizations-Omicron Delta Kappa, 1989 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Organizations-South Afric.Embassy materials, 1991 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Organizations-Support Center of Washington, 1990 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Organizations-Veterans Affairs, conference, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Organizations-World Wings International, 1988 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - PACE-Contract counseling, 1987 -1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - PACE-Contract course information, 1990 -1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - PACE-Hampton contracts, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - People-Adelman, Clifford, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - People-Altrusa-Sally Baffa, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - People-Brady, John Patrick, 1991 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - People-Colleagues, 1990 -1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - People-Trachtenberg, Stephen J., 1989 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Performance ratings, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Personal directives manual, 1975 -1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Personnel Locator, 1985 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Printing and graphics price list, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Publications/Media-announcements, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Publications/Media-George Washington University magazine, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Publications/Media-GWU television, 1992 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Publications/Media-GWU Times, vol. 10 no. 2, (3 copies), 03/1981 --04/1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Publications/Media-Humanities Council newsletter, 1990 -1991 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Publications/Media-International Associates newsletter, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Publications/Media-Newspaper articles, 1968 -1993 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Publications/Media-PBS information, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Recruitment-and retention of women and minority students at GW, 1988 -1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Recruitment-and retention of women and minority students at GW, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Request-New position, 06/1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reports-Annual reports, Division of University Programs, 1994 -1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reports-Annual reports, GSEHD (published), 1988 -1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Reports-Annual report, Kellogg Foundation, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Reports-Current weekly reports, 1970 ca. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Reports-Degrees confirmed, 1988 -1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Reports-Education reform initiatives and national mandates, 1963 -1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Reports-Historic study of establishment of the college of general studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Reports-Middle states GWU accreditation report, 1966 -1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Reports-Reallocation of resources, 09/30/1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Reports-Reallocation of resources, 12/11/1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Reports-School of Business and Public Management updated preliminary report, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Reports-Teaching report, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Resumes-Montgomery county high technology council resumes, 1991 -1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Resumes-Curriculum vitas, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Resumes-Job inquiries, 1990 -1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rice Hall-6th floor, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Small Groups, 1961 -1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Abbie-Assistant vice-president, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Abbie-Cavallaro, Patricia, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Abbie-Deanship, 1989 -1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Abbie-Dissertation, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Abbie-Education 701 paper, 12/20/1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Abbie-General office letters/personal, 1989 -1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Abbie-GW Award, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Abbie-Newspaper clippings, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Abbie-Past invitations, 1990 -1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Abbie-Recommendations, 1992 -1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Abbie-Reimbursement, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Abbie-Resume/curriculum vitae, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Abbie-Teaching, continuing higher education, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Abbie-Vacation/leave, 1991 -1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Planning- Katz Challenge, 01/22/1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - TOC (Training Officers Conference)-Annual Institute, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - TOC-Annual Institute, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - TOC-Annual Institute, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - TOC-Annual Institute, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - TOC-Correspondence, papers, 1985 -1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - TOC-Correspondence, papers, 1990 -1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - TOC-Correspondence, papers, 1990 -1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - TOC-Directory, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - TOC-Executive board, 1989 -1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - TOC-Executive board, 1990 -1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - TOC-Executive board, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - TOC-Executive board, 1992 -1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - TOC-Executive board retreat, 02/1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - TOC-Executive board retreat, 06/1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - TOC-Professional development program, 1989 -1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - TOC-Professional development series, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - TOC-Professional development series, 1991 -1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - TOC-Professional development series, 1992 -1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - TOC-Summer I, 1992 -1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Campus (GW owned), 1986 -1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Campus-Coordinating committee, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Campus-Task Force, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Visitors, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Volunteering, 1968 -1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Women's Continuing Education-AAUW conference on graduate and professional education of women, 05/09/1974 --05/10/1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Analysis of individual, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Annapolis, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Bumper stickers, 1974 -1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Career counseling for girls, 1972 ca. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Career development for employed women, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Career placement officer letter, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Career planning guide, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Discrimination Against Women: Hearings and sub-Committees in Congress, compiled in a book, 07/1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Final Report, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Handbook for administrators of C.E. for women Programs, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Historic.letters to Ruth Osborn from dev. new Horizons students, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Job information, 1965 ca. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Life/Career manual, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Manual, 1964 -1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Manual written by Ruth Osborn explaining the nature of Women's continuing education program at GW (binder), 1964 -1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Manual that counseled women on career development, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women's Continuing Education-National Convention, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Women's Continuing Education-National symphony program publicity, 1970 -1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Women's Continuing Education-New Horizons brochures, 1970 ca. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Women's Continuing Education-New Horizons brochures and notices, 1970 ca. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Women's Continuing Education-New Horizons class profiles, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Women's Continuing Education-New Horizons newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Newsletters, pamphlets, essays, 1972-1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Women's Continuing Education-NUCEA women's committee, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Our Bodies Our Selves, book, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Pamphlets, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - omen's Continuing Education-Pamphlets, papers, notes, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Re-entry programs in community colleges, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Social Work Course, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Syllabus, general information, 1974 ca. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Teacher Aides, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Various programs, 1975 ca. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Women's bureau, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Women's issues, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Women's Leadership Project, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Women's Continuing Education-"Women Moving Ahead", 1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Women's Continuing Education-Women's Research & Education Institute, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, "Monday Report", 10 year report, and schedule of classes, 1980-2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Center for Career Education Workshops (CCEW)- Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CCEW-Schedule of classes, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CCEW-Schedule of classes, 1987-1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education for Women (CEW)-Booklet, "Older Women: The Economics of Aging", 1969-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - CEW-brochures, 1969 ca. --1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CEW-brochures, 1969 ca. --1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - CEW & CCEW-brochures, 1968 -1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CEW & CCEW-brochures, 1968 -1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CEW/CGS Reorganization, 1980 -1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Chronologic files (CHRON), 07/1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CHRON, 08/1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CHRON, 09/1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - CHRON, 10/1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - CHRON, 11/1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - CHRON, 12/1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - CHRON, 06/1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)